let additionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 8 + 19",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 7",
        AnswerA: "28",
        AnswerB: "29",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 10",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "21",
        AnswerC: "22",
        AnswerD: "23",
        correctAnswer: "23",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 3",
        AnswerA: "39",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "41",
        AnswerD: "42",
        correctAnswer: "41",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 + 6",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "47",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 + 22",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 11 + 17",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 8",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "33",
        AnswerC: "34",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "34",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 + 19",
        AnswerA: "27",
        AnswerB: "28",
        AnswerC: "29",
        AnswerD: "30",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 + 17",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "43",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "45",
        correctAnswer: "42",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 + 17",
        AnswerA: "34",
        AnswerB: "35",
        AnswerC: "36",
        AnswerD: "37",
        correctAnswer: "34",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 + 15",
        AnswerA: "29",
        AnswerB: "30",
        AnswerC: "31",
        AnswerD: "32",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 16 + 16",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 + 18",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 + 19",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 20 + 20",
        AnswerA: "39",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 21 + 21",
        AnswerA: "40",
        AnswerB: "42",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "46",
        correctAnswer: "42",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 22 + 22",
        AnswerA: "44",
        AnswerB: "45",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "47",
        correctAnswer: "44",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 23",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "46",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 + 24",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "48",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 + 25",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "50",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 6",
        AnswerA: "27",
        AnswerB: "28",
        AnswerC: "29",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 + 18",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "33",
        AnswerC: "34",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "35",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 + 8",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 + 7",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 27",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 + 23",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "27",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 + 13",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 6 + 7",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "14",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 + 8",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 5 + 39",
        AnswerA: "43",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "46",
        correctAnswer: "44",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 + 9",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 + 19",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "66",
        AnswerC: "67",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 57",
        AnswerA: "80",
        AnswerB: "85",
        AnswerC: "90",
        AnswerD: "95",
        correctAnswer: "80",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 70",
        AnswerA: "81",
        AnswerB: "82",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "84",
        correctAnswer: "83",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 43",
        AnswerA: "78",
        AnswerB: "79",
        AnswerC: "80",
        AnswerD: "81",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 + 36",
        AnswerA: "62",
        AnswerB: "63",
        AnswerC: "64",
        AnswerD: "65",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 65 + 22",
        AnswerA: "86",
        AnswerB: "87",
        AnswerC: "88",
        AnswerD: "89",
        correctAnswer: "87",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 + 28",
        AnswerA: "63",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "66",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 48",
        AnswerA: "71",
        AnswerB: "72",
        AnswerC: "73",
        AnswerD: "74",
        correctAnswer: "74",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 69 + 19",
        AnswerA: "86",
        AnswerB: "87",
        AnswerC: "88",
        AnswerD: "89",
        correctAnswer: "88",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 45 + 37",
        AnswerA: "81",
        AnswerB: "82",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "84",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 + 27",
        AnswerA: "74",
        AnswerB: "75",
        AnswerC: "76",
        AnswerD: "77",
        correctAnswer: "74",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 + 35",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "70",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "80",
        correctAnswer: "70",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 46 + 11",
        AnswerA: "57",
        AnswerB: "58",
        AnswerC: "59",
        AnswerD: "60",
        correctAnswer: "57",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 58 + 17",
        AnswerA: "70",
        AnswerB: "75",
        AnswerC: "80",
        AnswerD: "85",
        correctAnswer: "85",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 61 + 19",
        AnswerA: "70",
        AnswerB: "80",
        AnswerC: "90",
        AnswerD: "100",
        correctAnswer: "80",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 50 + 50",
        AnswerA: "85",
        AnswerB: "90",
        AnswerC: "95",
        AnswerD: "100",
        correctAnswer: "100",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 + 41",
        AnswerA: "82",
        AnswerB: "84",
        AnswerC: "86",
        AnswerD: "88",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 + 22",
        AnswerA: "96",
        AnswerB: "97",
        AnswerC: "98",
        AnswerD: "99",
        correctAnswer: "99",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 + 23",
        AnswerA: "92",
        AnswerB: "93",
        AnswerC: "94",
        AnswerD: "95",
        correctAnswer: "95",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 34 + 24",
        AnswerA: "55",
        AnswerB: "56",
        AnswerC: "57",
        AnswerD: "58",
        correctAnswer: "58",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 + 4",
        AnswerA: "96",
        AnswerB: "97",
        AnswerC: "98",
        AnswerD: "99",
        correctAnswer: "97",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 82 + 11",
        AnswerA: "91",
        AnswerB: "92",
        AnswerC: "93",
        AnswerD: "94",
        correctAnswer: "93",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 65 + 18",
        AnswerA: "83",
        AnswerB: "84",
        AnswerC: "85",
        AnswerD: "86",
        correctAnswer: "83",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 + 28",
        AnswerA: "72",
        AnswerB: "73",
        AnswerC: "74",
        AnswerD: "75",
        correctAnswer: "75",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 66 + 7",
        AnswerA: "73",
        AnswerB: "74",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "76",
        correctAnswer: "73",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 59 + 22",
        AnswerA: "78",
        AnswerB: "79",
        AnswerC: "80",
        AnswerD: "81",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 33 + 23",
        AnswerA: "50",
        AnswerB: "55",
        AnswerC: "60",
        AnswerD: "65",
        correctAnswer: "55",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 58 + 13",
        AnswerA: "71",
        AnswerB: "72",
        AnswerC: "73",
        AnswerD: "74",
        correctAnswer: "71",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 56 + 21",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "76",
        AnswerC: "77",
        AnswerD: "78",
        correctAnswer: "77",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 51 + 27",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "76",
        AnswerC: "77",
        AnswerD: "78",
        correctAnswer: "78",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 + 39",
        AnswerA: "73",
        AnswerB: "74",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "76",
        correctAnswer: "74",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 29 + 25",
        AnswerA: "51",
        AnswerB: "52",
        AnswerC: "53",
        AnswerD: "54",
        correctAnswer: "54",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 88 + 29",
        AnswerA: "115",
        AnswerB: "116",
        AnswerC: "117",
        AnswerD: "118",
        correctAnswer: "117",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 97",
        AnswerA: "110",
        AnswerB: "115",
        AnswerC: "120",
        AnswerD: "125",
        correctAnswer: "120",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 113 + 12",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "125",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 103",
        AnswerA: "138",
        AnswerB: "139",
        AnswerC: "140",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "141",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 + 106",
        AnswerA: "145",
        AnswerB: "146",
        AnswerC: "147",
        AnswerD: "148",
        correctAnswer: "147",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 115 + 22",
        AnswerA: "136",
        AnswerB: "137",
        AnswerC: "138",
        AnswerD: "139",
        correctAnswer: "137",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 111 + 17",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "128",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 118",
        AnswerA: "141",
        AnswerB: "142",
        AnswerC: "143",
        AnswerD: "144",
        correctAnswer: "144",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 + 119",
        AnswerA: "127",
        AnswerB: "128",
        AnswerC: "129",
        AnswerD: "130",
        correctAnswer: "128",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 + 117",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "142",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 + 27",
        AnswerA: "141",
        AnswerB: "142",
        AnswerC: "143",
        AnswerD: "144",
        correctAnswer: "144",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 115 + 15",
        AnswerA: "129",
        AnswerB: "130",
        AnswerC: "131",
        AnswerD: "132",
        correctAnswer: "130",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 116 + 17",
        AnswerA: "131",
        AnswerB: "132",
        AnswerC: "133",
        AnswerD: "134",
        correctAnswer: "133",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 118 + 23",
        AnswerA: "138",
        AnswerB: "139",
        AnswerC: "140",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "141",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 119 + 7",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "126",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 + 45",
        AnswerA: "122",
        AnswerB: "123",
        AnswerC: "124",
        AnswerD: "125",
        correctAnswer: "122",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 74 + 38",
        AnswerA: "110",
        AnswerB: "111",
        AnswerC: "112",
        AnswerD: "113",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 83 + 39",
        AnswerA: "121",
        AnswerB: "122",
        AnswerC: "123",
        AnswerD: "124",
        correctAnswer: "122",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 94 + 23",
        AnswerA: "116",
        AnswerB: "117",
        AnswerC: "118",
        AnswerD: "119",
        correctAnswer: "117",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 68 + 47",
        AnswerA: "114",
        AnswerB: "115",
        AnswerC: "116",
        AnswerD: "117",
        correctAnswer: "115",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 64 + 61",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "125",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 116",
        AnswerA: "138",
        AnswerB: "139",
        AnswerC: "140",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "139",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 + 25",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "142",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 + 9",
        AnswerA: "123",
        AnswerB: "124",
        AnswerC: "125",
        AnswerD: "126",
        correctAnswer: "126",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 83 + 41",
        AnswerA: "124",
        AnswerB: "125",
        AnswerC: "126",
        AnswerD: "127",
        correctAnswer: "124",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 87 + 36",
        AnswerA: "123",
        AnswerB: "124",
        AnswerC: "125",
        AnswerD: "126",
        correctAnswer: "123",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 112 + 34",
        AnswerA: "144",
        AnswerB: "145",
        AnswerC: "146",
        AnswerD: "147",
        correctAnswer: "146",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 106 + 28",
        AnswerA: "131",
        AnswerB: "132",
        AnswerC: "133",
        AnswerD: "134",
        correctAnswer: "134",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 100 + 50",
        AnswerA: "135",
        AnswerB: "140",
        AnswerC: "145",
        AnswerD: "150",
        correctAnswer: "150",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 + 47",
        AnswerA: "119",
        AnswerB: "120",
        AnswerC: "121",
        AnswerD: "122",
        correctAnswer: "119",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 98 + 39",
        AnswerA: "137",
        AnswerB: "138",
        AnswerC: "139",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "137",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 86 + 27",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "113",
    },
]